orange-themes.com 2016-11-19

# Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

This policy covers how we use your personal information. We take your privacy seriously and will take all measures to protect your personal information. Any personal information received will only be used to fill your order (no credit card information will be stored on our servers). We will not sell or redistribute your information to anyone. Your email address will be used to notify you of upcoming updates and news. You may, of course permanently unsubscribe anytime you wish to stop receiving our newsletter.

### We collect the following personal information from you

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  * Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.

### We use this information to

  * Fulfill your order
  * Send you an order confirmation
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Respond to your questions and messages

## Security

When we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
